Finding aid for Interlochen Center for The Arts Records, 1927-2005
Bentley Historical Library
- Photographs: Prints, 1880-1986
  - Early Camp, 1927-1945 (mainly 1927-1942)
    - Boys camp (panoramic view), circa, 1931 (Box 73)
      (see also oversized folder, UBImul/C367)
      (39)
    - Brass groups
      - Circa (mainly by cottages), 1928-1931 (Box 73)
        (40)
      - Circa, 1932-1936 (Box 73)
        (41)
    - Buildings (exterior and interior)
      - A-Z, circa, 1930s; 1945 (Box 73)
        (42)
      - Unidentified, circa, 1929-1936 (Box 73)
        (43)
    - Cabin groups
      - Female
        - Circa, 1928-1930 (Box 73)
          (44)
        - Circa, 1931 (Box 73)
          (45)
        - Circa, 1932-1935 (Box 73)
          (46)
        - Circa, 1936-1937 (Box 73)
          (47)
      - Male
        - Circa, 1928-1929 (Box 73)
          (48)
        - Circa, 1930-1931 (Box 73)
          (49)
        - Circa, 1932-1936 (Box 73)
          (50)
    - Camp activities
      (see also Sports and Recreation)
      - Circa, 1929-1937 (Box 73)
        (51)
      - Circa, 1938-1942 (Box 73)
        (52)
    - Camp Penn Loch, 1928 (Folder UBImul/367)
      (53)
    - Camp groups
      (oversized)
      - With Maddy, Giddings and Pennington, 1929 (Box 73)
      - With Maddy, Giddings and Pennington, 1930 (Box 73)
      - With Maddy and Giddings, 1938 (Box 73)
    - Campers (mainly individuals with instruments)
      - Identified by name, circa, 1929-1940; 1944-1945 (Box 73)
        (54)
      - Unidentified
        - Circa, 1928-1941 (Box 73)
          (55)
        - Circa, 1942 (Box 73)
          (56)
    - Campers in large groups (unidentified)
      - Outdoors by dorms, circa, 1930-1931 (Box 73)
        (57)
      - In Bowl (entire camp?, including with Maddy and Giddings), circa, 1934-1937 (Box 73)
        (58)
    - Campers, former (identified), circa, 1938-1943 (Box 73)
      (59)
    - Cartoons
      - 1942-1953, 2 folders (Box 73)
        (59a)
    - Cello groups, circa, 1929-1936 (Box 73)
      (60)
    - Choral groups, circa, 1928-1942 (Box 73)
      (61)
    - College Division Band at Michigan Day of Chicago World's Fair with Gov. William Comstock, 1933 (Folder UBImul/C367)
    - Composition classes, circa, 1934-1936 (Box 73)
      (62)
    - Concerts in Interlochen Bowl
      - Performances, circa, 1928-1941 (Box 73)
        (63)
      - Crowds, circa, 1928-1930s (Box 73)
        (64)
    - Conducting classes (including with Bakalienekoff and Harrison), circa 1930-1942 (Box 73)
      (65)
    - Construction of facilities
      - Pre-Camp, circa, 1927-1928
        - Initial stages (Box 73)
          (66)
        - Buildings rising (Box 73)
          (67)
        - Final stages (Box 73)
          (68)
      - Interlochen Bowl, circa, 1927-1930 (Box 73)
        (69)
      - Other projects, circa, 1929-1942 (Box 73)
        (70)
    - Damrosch, Walter
      - Conducting, circa, 1936 (Box 73)
        (71)
      - General, circa late, 1930s (Box 73)
        (72)
    - Dancers (individual female Campers), 1940 (Box 73)
      (73)
    - Dining Hall-male (exterior and interior), circa, 1931 (Box 73)
      (74)
    - Dormitory scenes (mainly interior), circa, 1929-1942 (Box 73)
      (75)
    - Drama productions (including Native American motif), circa, 1930s (Box 73)
      (76)
    - Drum major classes, circa, 1929-1942 (Box 73)
      (77)
    - Dunham, Franklin (Trustee), circa, 1940 (Box 73)
      (78)
    - Ensembles (mixed), circa, 1928-1940 (Box 73)
      (79)
    - Faculty and staff portraits, circa, 1930-1945
      - A-C (Box 73)
        (80)
      - D-F (Box 73)
        (81)
      - G-K (Box 73)
        (82)
      - L (Box 73)
        (83)
      - M (Box 73)
        (84)
      - N-Q (Box 73)
        (85)
      - R-T (Box 73)
        (86)
      - U-Z (Box 73)
        (87)
    - Faculty and staff groups, including with Maddy and Giddings, circa, 1928-1932; 1938 (Box 73)
      (88)
    - Faculty and staff miscellaneous, circa, 1928-1945 (Box 73)
      (89)
    - Faculty and staff applicants (not hired?), 1938-1945 (Box 73)
      (90)
    - Faculty with Campers, circa, 1937-1942
      - A-L (Box 73)
        (91)
      - M-Z (Box 73)
        (92)
    - Fennell, Frederick (Box 73)
      (93)
    - Giddings, Thaddeus P.
      - By self (at Interlochen), circa, 1928-1942 (Box 73)
        (94)
      - With others, including Maddy circa, 1928-1940 (Box 73)
        (95)
    - Grainger, Percy, circa, 1930-1942 (Box 73)
      (96)
    - Grounds and scenic views
      - Lake views, circa, 1928-1930s (Box 73)
        (97)
      - Woods and pathways, circa, 1930s (Box 73)
        (98)
      - Winter scenes (hotel and Bowl), circa, 1930s (Box 73)
        (99)
    - Guest conductors
      - Portraits, circa, 1928-1942 (Box 73)
        (100)
      - In groups, circa, 1928-1942 (Box 73)
        (101)
      - With students, circa, 1928-1942 (Box 73)
        (102)
      - Miscellaneous (humorous welcome?), circa, 1936 (Box 73)
        (103)
      - Guest cottages (?), circa, 1930s (Box 73)
        (104)
      - Hanson, Howard, circa, 1928-1942 (Box 73)
        (105)
      - Harp playing groups, circa, 1928-1936 (Box 73)
        (106)
      - Hoffmaster, Maud Miller, circa, 1940-1945 (Box 73)
        (107)
      - Hospital scenes, circa, 1929-1940 (Box 73)
        (108)
      - Hotel Exterior and interior circa, 1929-1940 (Box 73)
        (109)
      - Hotel Pennington postcards, circa, 1928-1932 (Box 73)
        (110)
    - Instrument Classes, circa, 1929-1936 (Box 73)
      (111)
    - Interlochen State Park, circa, 1928-1938 (Box 73)
      (112)
    - Library, circa, 1930-1940 (Box 73)
      (113)
    - Maazel, Lorin, 1939 (Box 74)
    - Marching bands, 1929 (Box 74)
    - McConkey, George (Camp architect), circa, 1928 (Box 74)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Identified individuals, circa, 1928-1942 (Box 74)
      - Buses considered for purchase, 1945 (Box 74)
    - Movies
      - Paramount: "There's Magic in Music" (publicity shots), 1941-1942 (Box 74)
      - Orchestra during Pathe newsreel filming, 1930 (Box 74)
    - Opera
      - "Telawalla," circa, 1930s (Box 74)
      - "Faust", 1936 (Box 74)
    - Operetta (Gilbert and Sullivan)
      - Circa, 1929-1935 (Box 74)
      - 1942 (Box 74)
        (including participation of Governor Van Wagoner)
    - Organizations (women) meeting at Interlochen, circa, 1930s (Box 74)
    - Pennington, Willis (portraits), 1929; 1931 (Box 74)
    - Percussion classes (including with Fennell), circa, 1929-1942 (Box 74)
    - Piano classes, circa, 1929-1936 (Box 74)
    - Practice buildings, studios, and rooms, circa, 1929-1935 (Box 74)
    - Radio classes, 1938-1942 (Box 74)
    - Railroad station at Interlochen, circa, 1930 (Box 74)
      (see also Box 1, 103)
    - Saxophone groups, circa, 1929-1930s (Box 74)
    - Scrapbook compiled by James Reynolds, 1932 (Box 74)
      (19a)
    - Sousa, John Philip
      - Portraits, 1930; 1931 (Box 74)
      - Conducting at Interlochen, 1930-1931 (Box 74)
      - With friends and associates, 1930-1931 (Box 74)
      - Memorial plaque, 1936 (Box 74)
    - Sports and recreation
      (see also Camp Activities)
      - Calisthenics (group), circa, 1930-1936 (Box 74)
      - Canoeing, circa, 1930 (Box 74)
      - Miscellaneous, circa, 1932-1935 (Box 74)
      - Swimming, circa, 1929-1936 (Box 74)
      - Tennis, circa, 1928-1932 (Box 74)
    - Stock, Frederick, 1940-1941 (Box 74)
    - String classes
      - Groups, circa, 1930-1936 (Box 74)
      - Performing, circa, 1936-1942 (Box 74)
    - Traverse City, Cherry Festival Parade 1929 and circa 1932, 1929-1932 (Box 74)
    - Tremaine, Charles Milton, circa, 1920s; 1940s (Box 74)
    - Vandenberg, Mrs. Arthur H. and daughter Betty, circa, 1930 (Box 74)
    - Vocal Methods class (with Giddings), 1936-1938 (Box 74)
    - Woodwind groups, circa, 1930-1936 (Box 74)
    - World's Fair appearance (New York), 1939 (Box 74)
  - Later Camp and Academy, 1946-1996; 1948-1979
    The later Camp/Academy portion, largely 1948-1984, is far less extensive. In 1942, having built a darkroom, Interlochen began maintaining its own photo archives. Although some later prints have been added through manuscript accessions, the archives at Interlochen remains the best source of photographs on its recent history.
    Despite the limitations of the post-1942 prints, they include some interesting images. They cover Van Cliburn's and Luci Baines Johnson's appearances, Alden Dow's architectural work, C.S. Mott's building dedication, and Werner von Braun's visit with his Camper daughter as well as the ISME meeting with participants Norman Dello Joio, Demitri Kabalevsky, and Zoltan Kodaly.
    - Art displays, circa, 1960s (Box 74)
    - Camp Orchestra performing Olympics, Atlanta, GA, 1996 (Box 74)
      (38a)
    - Campers
      - Young girls groups, circa, 1950s (Box 74)
      - Instrumental groups (postcards), circa, 1960s (Box 74)
    - Cliburn, Van (practice with Maddy and Wilson conducting the orchestra), circa, 1960s (Box 74)
    - Concerts at Interlochen
      - Performances in Interlochen Bowl, circa, 1950s; 1960s (Box 74)
      - Crowd outside Kresge Auditorium, circa, 1960s (Box 74)
    - Conn centennial celebration, 1975 (Box 74)
    - Craft classes, circa, 1967 (Box 74)
    - Detroit Symphony Orchestra in residence at the IAA, 1992 (Box 74)
      (45a)
    - Dow, Alden, explaining to Academy staff the proposed layout of the Performing Arts Center, 1969 (Box 74)
    - Electronic Classes, circa, 1949-1954 (Box 74)
    - Federation of Music Clubs
      - Scenes at Scholarship Lodges, 1954-1955 (Box 74)
      - Michigan convention (with Maddy, Morton Gould, and Lloyd Grinnell), 1955 (Box 74)
      - National 1966 and circa 1974, 1966-1974 (Box 74)
    - Federation of Women's Clubs (Michigan convention), 1970 (Box 74)
    - Fourth of July, International students and flags, 1987 (Box 74)
      (51a)
    - Freedom Train concert (Grand Rapids), 1948 (Box 74)
    - Froligh, Edward P. (Trustee), circa, 1969 (Box 74)
    - Fund raising activities, circa, 1964-1966 (Box 74)
    - Funeral, Joseph Maddy, 1966 (Box 74)
      (54a)
    - Grand Traverse Performing Arts Center (architectural renderings by Alden Dow Associates), 1968 (Box 74)
    - Guest conductor with students, circa, 1960s (Box 74)
    - Historical marker dedication (Maddy, Bonisteel, and Louis Vander Velde), 1962 (Box 74)
    - Hotel, circa, 1957-1970 (Box 74)
    - Interlochen Arts Academy
      - Opening concert, 1962 (Box 74)
      - Campus scenes, 1960s; 1970s (Box 74)
      - Performances
        - Orchestra (with Maddy and Thor Johnson conducting), circa, 1964-1973 (Box 74)
        - Post-performance party in New York, circa, 1960s (Box 74)
        - Drama (Interlochen Outreach for elementary schools), 1971 (Box 74)
    - Interlochen Arts Festival, circa, 1964 (Box 74)
    - International Society of Music Educators, 1966
      - Dello Joio, Norman (Box 74)
      - Kabalevsky, Demitri (Box 74)
      - Kodaly, Zoltan and others (Box 74)
    - Johnson, Luci Baines (with Maddy and Van Cliburn), 1964 (Box 74)
    - Maddy Administration Building (postcard), 1953 (Box 74)
    - Miscellaneous (identified individuals), circa, 1960s (Box 74)
    - Mott, C. S. (with Maddy at dedication of Mott Building), circa, 1965 (Box 74)
    - Norman, Jessye, 1968 (Box 74)
      (71a)
    - Osterlin Wishing Well, undated (Box 74)
      (71b)
    - Paulson, Thom, 1992 (Box 74)
      (71c)
    - Schub, Andre-Michel (Van Cliburn winner), 1981 (Box 74)
    - Stone Student Center dedication, 1964 (Box 74)
      (72a)
    - Toradze, Lexo (Van Cliburn winner), 1979-1984 (Box 74)
    - U.S. (Air Force?) Band, circa, 1960s (Box 74)
    - Van Cliburn conducting, 1964 (Box 74)
      (74a)
    - Von Braun, Werner, with Camper daughter and Egon Kraus, 1966 (Box 74)
    - Watergate (Washington, D.C.) concert, 1964 (Box 74)
    - World Youth Symphony
      - With Haas, Wilson, and Van Cliburn, circa, 1969 (Box 74)
      - Rehearsing with Eugene Ormandy, 1964 (Box 74)
        (77a)
  - Later administrators, mainly 1957-78
    Prints of later administrators, mainly 1957-1978, came with their papers. Wilson's (1930-1978) include a few images of him as an early Camper and as a civic music conductor. Most emphasize his activities as Camp Director, including the visit of Mrs. Imelda Marcos and the dedication of the National Music Camp of the Philippines.
    Don Gillis' photos (circa 1959) highlight his work for Interlochen. They include scenes of American Opera Theatre productions and the visit of American Federation of Musicians officials, which ended the Petrillo controversy.
    The Administrative Committee is shown in session, circa 1966-1967 while the Karl Haas' images, 1967, focus on his selection and inauguration as President of Interlochen. The latter show Haas meeting with members of the Administrative Committee and Board of Trustees and being installed as President.
    Though few in number, Jacobi's photographs (1975-1986) include images of him and his staff with George Wilson (1978) and of President and Mrs. Gerald Ford's visit to Interlochen (1975).
    - Eilber, Charles and a new student, circa, 1968 (Box 74)
      (77b)
    - Gillis, Donald
      - Portraits, circa, 1959; undated (Box 74)
      - American Federation of Musicians visit (with Maddy), 1959 (Box 74)
      - American Opera Workshop, 2 folders (Box 74)
        (80-81)
      - Toscanini, Arturo (Box 74)
    - Administrative Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 74)
    - Haas, Karl
      - Portraits, circa, 1967 (Box 74)
      - Trustees meeting in Detroit (announcement of selection as president?), 1967 (Box 74)
      - Trustees and administrative committee meeting at Inglis House in Ann Arbor, 1967 (Box 74)
      - Inauguration as president (with Bonisteel and Hatcher), 1967 (Box 74)
      - Brahms manuscript (gift), 1967 (Box 74)
      - Dance scholarship winner at Camp (with Wilson), 1967 (Box 74)
      - Fund raising (with Mrs. Maddy, Mrs. Stone, Bonisteel, Ann Ronell, and Lester Cowan), circa, 1968-1969 (Box 74)
      - Miscellaneous (identified individuals: Nissman and Stadler), circa, 1967-1969 (Box 74)
    - Rideout, Raymond greeting new students, 1993 (Box 74)
      (91a)
    - Wilson, George
      - Individual and group, circa, 1930-1978 (Box 74)
      - Civic Music
        - Ann Arbor Civic Orchestra, circa, 1950s (Box 74)
        - Northwest Michigan Symphony, 1966 (Box 74)
      - Philippines
        - Mrs. Marcos visits the Camp (also shows Jacobi and other staff), 1973 (Box 74)
        - Dedication of its National Arts Center (with Mrs. Marcos), 1973 (Box 74)
        - Filipino campers and visitors, 1973 (Box 74)
    - Jacobi, Roger
      - 50th anniversary of Camp, receipt of resolution from state legislature, 1977 (Box 74)
      - Ford, President and Mrs. Gerald, visit Camp (also shows Clement Stone), 1975 (Box 74)
      - Wilson, George, presenting his oral history tape at a staff meeting, 1986 (Box 74)
      - Portraits-formal and informal (Box 74)
      - Academy opening, 1979 (Box 74)
      - Administration
        - Jacobi
          - With Galbraith and Downing, 1982; undated (Box 74)
          - With others-staff, students, and guests, 1971; 1973; undated (Box 74)
        - Downing, Edward J.-Camp Director (Box 74)
        - Galbraith, Bruce W.-Academy Director (Box 74)
      - Alcantara, Theo (Box 74)
      - Buildings
        - Grand Traverse Area Performing Arts Center-interior views (Box 74)
        - Construction scenes (GTPAC?)-with student string quartet playing and distinguished guests present (Box 74)
        - Various buildings (Box 74)
      - Camp
        - Staff group (photography?), 1977 (Box 74)
        - Students
          - With instructor and guest (Box 74)
          - Intermediate orchestra performance (Box 74)
            (114)
          - With noise makers in balcony (Box 74)
            (115)
      - Campus scene in fall (Box 74)
        (116)
      - Cliburn, Van-performing with Camp orchestra-George Wilson conducting (Box 74)
        (117)
      - Danish medallion presentation-Rebild Society, Jens Schroeder and Jacobi (Box 74)
        (118)
      - Hope, Bob, visit-with Jacobi, Clement Stone and George Wilson (Box 74)
        (119)
      - Presidential Scholar in the Arts, Scott Van Ornum, on White House lawn with Jacobi and Galbraith, 1984 (Box 74)
        (120)
      - Rostropovich, Mstislav-with Jacobi, Downing, and Henry Clark Smith, 1992 (Box 74)
        (121)
      - Schuller, Gunther-with World Youth Symphony, 1973 (Box 74)
        (123)
      - Sculptures (Box 74)
        (124)
      - Suzuki violin student-promotional shot of young child standing by Interlochen poster, 1972 (Box 74)
        (125)
      - Trustees
        - Group-meeting at Interlochen, including Stone and William Milliken (Box 74)
          (126)
        - Ford, Christina (?) with Jacobi (Box 74)
          (127)
        - Keith, Damon with Jacobi and Camp orchestra (Box 74)
          (128)
        - Marvel, David (also Vice President for Development) with Jacobi and others (Box 74)
          (129)
        - Patterson, W. Calvin (Box 74)
          (130)
        - Vance, Ruth (Mrs. Joseph A.) (Box 74)
          (131)
      - University of Michigan Regents meeting at Interlochen, Jacobi addressing and Camp students performing, 1980 (Box 74)
        (132)
      - Warsaw Philharmonic leaders with Polish Campers and Jacobi, 1982 (Box 74)
        (133)
    - Boal, Dean, 1994 (Box 74)
      (133a)
- Photographs: Negatives, 1 folder
  Less than 100 photographic Negatives (2), circa 1931-1938, are included in the collection (two others made from our print holdings are part of the library's negative files). All are nitrate and date from the 1930's. Six show Maddy's radio band classes at the U. of M. (in studio and on campus), circa 1931-1937.
  The remainder (91) were apparently taken of Camp activities during the summer of 1938. Some of them were used in article about the Camp which appeared in the musical journal True Tone, in the fall 1938 (a copy of which is included with the negatives) and subsequent Camp publications. They show activities of Campers, adult visitors, and guests as well as an appearance by the Camp band and orchestra at the National Cherry Festival in Traverse City, July 13-15, 1938. Maddy probably took most of them since he appears in only one. Seven of the images have prints (see 1), all apparently from 1938: one of Maddy speaking at Interlochen and six of other Camp scenes.
  - Maddy, circa, 1931-1937
    - Radio band class, U. of M. (Box 74)
      (1-7)
  - Early Camp, circa, 1938
    - Assembly with Maddy speaking (print in box l, #30) (Box 74)
    - Camp activities
      - Campers by hotel (Box 74)
      - Campers (female) on bench (Box 74)
    - Campers unidentified
      - Female organist with two others (Box 74)
      - Female pianist (Box 74)
      - Female violinist (two views, print of one in box 1, #54) (Box 74)
        (13-14)
    - Composition class of William Skeat outside little red schoolhouse (Box 74)
    - Concerts in Interlochen Bowl
      - Pianist and violinist; audience on stage (Box 74)
    - Conducting class
      - With Bakaleinikoff-posed group (Box 74)
      - Students practicing (Box 74)
    - Dining hall
      - Serving line (three views) (Box 74)
        (19-21)
      - At tables (Box 74)
    - Dormitory scenes
      - Boy in bunk (two views) (Box 74)
        (23-24)
    - Drum major class with Overgard (Box 74)
    - Faculty with Campers
      - Students writing in classroom (Schram's class?) (Box 74)
    - Individual instruction
      - Bass viol (Box 74)
      - Piano (Box 74)
      - Trombone (Box 74)
    - Giddings with associates
      - Herbert Clarke (?) (Box 74)
      - Group including Clarke (?) (Box 74)
    - Grolle, John, visitor to Camp (Box 74)
    - Guest conductors
      - Bakaleinikoff, Vladimir on walk (Box 74)
        (print in box 1, #100)
      - Harrison, Guy Fraser, conducting (Box 74)
        (34-38)
        (five views, print of one in box l, #102)
      - Gagnier (?), sitting on log by lake (Box 74)
      - Schram, Rudolph
        (?)
        - Playing violin in woods (Box 74)
        - With orchestra in practice room (Box 74)
        - With orchestra in Interlochen Bowl (two views) (Box 74)
          (42-43)
      - Group (Harrison, Overgard, and Grofe ?) on dock (Box 74)
      - Unidentified with orchestra in Interlochen Bowl (Box 74)
    - Guest cottage (Box 74)
    - Hanson, Howard
      - Conducting (print in box 1, #105) (Box 74)
      - Class, showing Maddy (print in box l, #105) (Box 74)
    - Hotel dining room
      - Individual groups (two views) (Box 74)
        (49-50)
      - Women's organization meeting (Box 74)
      - Musicians playing for diners (Box 74)
    - Miscellaneous-unidentified young woman by hotel (Box 74)
    - Percussion classes
      - In class (Box 74)
      - Leaving class (Box 74)
    - Radio class
      - Boutwell (?) instructing (Box 74)
      - Staff picnic (print in box 2, #17) (Box 74)
    - Reed section playing (two views) (Box 74)
      (58-59)
    - Sports and recreation
      - Calisthenics (boys) (Box 74)
      - Canoeing
        - Couple (Box 74)
        - Two men (Box 74)
      - Dancing, ballroom (five views)-adults at (party?)
        (63-67)
        - Maddy catch (?) (Box 74)
        - Boy fishing from bank (Box 74)
        - Small boy fishing from bank (Box 74)
        - Man on bank (Box 74)
        - Man in stream (Box 74)
      - Miscellaneous adult
        - Two females on beach (Box 74)
        - Boating and picnicking (Box 74)
        - Male with feet in water and plate in hand (Box 74)
        - Group on shore (Box 74)
        - Group on shore, on dock, and in boat (Box 74)
        - Couple on lakefront (Box 74)
        - Two males seated on lake shore (Box 74)
        - Two males on dock (Box 74)
      - Swimming instruction (Box 74)
      - Tennis-girls playing-musicians watching (two views) (Box 74)
        (82-83)
      - Water skiing (Box 74)
    - Traverse City Cherry Festival
      - Parade
        - As seen from atop downtown building (four views) (Box 74)
          (85-88)
        - Camper musicians on break (Box 74)
        - Two adult males dressed as Keystone Cops with female Camp musicians, crowd in background (note: this was originally labeled Allan Grant and NBC music staff) (Box 74)
      - Concert
        - Cherry Queen (?) with McAllister and Overgard (?) (two views) (Box 74)
          (91-92)
        - Two men shaking hands in front of orchestra (two views) (Box 74)
          (93-94)
        - Young boy playing conductor (Box 74)
        - Accordionist performing (Box 74)
        - Movie cameraman at work (Box 74)
- Oversized Photographs
  - Maddy
    - Early career
      - Santa Fe Boys, Wellington, Kansas, circa, 1905 (Box 75)
      - Metropolitan Quintet, Wichita Falls, Texas, circa, 1914 (Box 75)
    - Mother (Mary Elizabeth Maddy) and art work, circa 1920s; 2 prints (Box 75)
    - Portrait with campus plans, circa, 1965 (Box 75)
    - Portrait, undated (Box 75)
    - Appearances, State High School groups, including Michigan, 1924-1955; 16 prints (Box 75)
    - Music Educators National Conference, banquet, 1938 (Box 75)
  - National High School Orchestra, 1926-1930; 1938; 15 prints
    (includes photos with President Hoover and Senator Vandenberg)
    - Camp groups, including orchestra, band, faculty, and staff
      - 1928-1931, 19 prints (Box 75)
      - 1932-1938, 19 prints (Box 75)
    - Concerts in Interlochen Bowl, including with Sousa conducting, 1928-1931; 9 prints (Box 75)
    - Michigan All-State Band, Masonic Temple, Detroit, 1939 (Box 75)
- Visual Materials: Glass slides